Finding Aid for the Stanley Chase Papers LSC.1090
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 2: Film, 1955-2001.; 38 boxes, 4 oversize boxes, 18 map folders.
  - Subseries 2F: Scripts, 1956-2001.; 19 Boxes.
    - Matheson, Richard. Hell House., no date. (Box 108, Folder 6)
      Chase-Matheson Productions.
    - Ashley, Wilson. The Nightclerk., no date. (Box 108, Folder 7)
      Outline and screenplay based on the novel by Stephen Schneck. Stanley Chase Productions.
    - Smith, William Dale. Man on Fire., no date. (Box 109, Folder 1)
      Based on the novel by A.J. Quinnell. Aldrich Company Paul Heller Production.
    - Attanasio, Paul. Donnie Brasco., 1996. (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Dozier, Bob and Frank Conroy. When the Legends Die., 1968 August 7. (Box 109, Folder 3)
      No. 26556. Based on the book by Hal Borland. Universal City Studios.
    - Knop, Patricia Louisianna. Silence of the Night., 1978 February 5. (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Minghella, Anthony. The English Patient., no date. (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Thompson, Emma. Sense and Sensibility., 1995 April 17. (Box 109, Folder 6)
      Adaptation of the novel by Jane Austen. Columbia Pictures.
    - Foote, Horton. Convicts., no date. (Box 110, Folder 1)
      Del Rio Films.
    - Odell, David. Chicago, Chicago., 1974 September 30. (Box 110, Folder 2)
      Based on the book by Elmore Leonard. Tomorrow Entertainment, INC.
    - Underhill, Frederic. Black Sun., 1976 April. (Box 110, Folder 3)
      Based on the novel by Edward Abbey. WGA West.
    - Kyle: A 21st Century Detective Story., 1970 September 14. (Box 110, Folder 4)
      Apjac Productions, INC.
    - Cunningham, E.V. The Case of the Russian Diplomat: a Masao Masuto Detective Story., no date. (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Roth, Eric. The Danger., no date. (Box 110, Folder 6)
      Vista Films.
    - Gallico, Paul. Love, Let me not Hunger., 1973. (Box 110, Folder 7)
      Foote, Comb and Belding Productions.
    - Stefano, Joseph. Svengali., no date. (Box 111, Folder 1)
      Alan Landsburg Productions.
    - Richardson, Jack. Underworld: A Musical., 1980. (Box 111, Folder 2)
      Adapted from John Gay's The Beggar's Opera; based on an idea by Elliot Silverstein. Underworld Productions.
    - Petersen, Wolfgang. The Plastic Nightmare., no date. (Box 111, Folder 3)
      Based on a novel by Richard Neely. Edgar J. Scherick Associates, INC.
    - Bridges, James. Chocolate Milk., no date. (Box 111, Folder 4)
      First draft treatment for a movie musical.
    - Howard, Alan. Out of the Blue., no date. (Box 111, Folder 5)
      Stanley Chase Productions.
    - Pittman, Mark. Under the Gun., no date. (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Axelrod, Jonathan and Stanley Chase. Jackson's Company., no date. (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Chase, Stanley and Bill Svanoe. The Killing of Jack the Ripper., no date. (Box 111, Folder 8)
      Treatment by Bill Svanoe. Alan Landsburg Productions.
    - The Trial at Wounded Knee., no date. (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - McGrath, Earl. The Free Way., 1968 March 5. (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Kleiner, Harry. An Agent in Place., no date. (Box 112, Folder 2)
      Comments.
    - Starr, Ben. The April Fools., 1966. (Box 112, Folder 3)
      Second draft screenplay and notes.
    - Serling, Rod. The Devil in Paradise., 1968 January 20. (Box 112, Folder 4)
      Based on the novel by Max Evans.
    - Matheson, Richard. Trilemma., no date. (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - O'Hanlon, George. Two's a Crowd., no date. (Box 112, Folder 6)
      A comedy in two acts.
    - Karpf, Stephen and Elinor. Billyboy., 1968 January 15. (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Sobelman, Boris and Jack Robinson. Bluebonnet., no date. (Box 112, Folder 8)
      Synopsis.
    - Armitage, George. Groupie., no date. (Box 112, Folder 9)
      Treatment.
    - Cornyn, Stan. The Night Action., 1966 May 11. (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Dalrymple, Andrew. God Bless Us, Every One!, no date. (Box 113, Folder 2)
      Sequel to A Christmas Carol. Stanley Chase Productions.
    - Chase, Stanley. "I Am Somebody.", no date. (Box 113, Folder 3)
      One-page synopsis.
    - Traverse, Claude. Midnight Call., no date. (Box 113, Folder 4)
      CBS Friday Night Movie, Stanley Chase, producer. Based on The Crack Up by Stanley Chase and David Z. Goodman. Screen gems.
    - Chase, Stanley. The Yablonski Case., no date. (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Bartel, Paul. Mixed Nuts., no date. (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Jarrico, Paul. The Man in the Iron Mask., 1972 August 26. (Box 113, Folder 7)
      Based on the novel by Alexandre Dumas.
    - Ling, Wang Hui, et. al. Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon., no date. (Box 113, Folder 8)
      Based on the novel by Wang Du Lu.
    - Festinger, Rob and Todd Field. In the Bedroom., no date. (Box 113, Folder 9)
      Based on the short story "Killings" by Andre Dubus.
    - Whedon, Joss, et. al. Toy Story., no date. (Box 114, Folder 1)
      Disney.
    - Harrison, William and Bob Rafelson. Mountains of the Moon., 1988 August. (Box 114, Folder 2)
      Shooting script. William Morris Agency.
    - Tarantino, Quentin. Reservoir Dogs., 1990 October 22. (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Roth, Eric and Michael Mann. The Insider., no date. (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Leigh, Mike. Topsy-Turvey., no date. (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Kaufman, Charlie. Being John Malkovich., 1998. (Box 114, Folder 6)
      Propaganda Films.
    - Condon, Bill. Gods and Monsters., 1997 May 30. (Box 114, Folder 7)
      Based on the novel Father of Frankenstein by Christopher Bram.
    - Darabont, Frank. The Green Mile., no date. (Box 114, Folder 8)
      Based on the serial novel by Stephen King. Castle Rock Entertainment.
    - Leonard, Elmore. The Hunted., no date. (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Howard, Alan. Sweet Deception., 1980 October 6. (Box 115, Folder 2)
      Synopsis of a screenplay. Warner Bros.
    - Howard, Alan. California Natural., no date. (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Boorman, John. Beyond Rangoon., 1993 November 5. (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Sharp, Alan. Billy Two Hats., 1972. (Box 115, Folder 5)
      First draft screenplay. Laup Productions.
    - Burns, Allan. Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid, Part One., no date. (Box 115, Folder 6)
      Prequel. Pantheon Pictures.
    - Pavigano, Anna, et. al. The Postman / Il Postino., no date. (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Helgeland, Brian and Hanson, Curtis. L.A. Confidential., 1996. (Box 115, Folder 8)
      Based on the novel by James Ellroy. New Regency Productions.
    - Frank, Scott. Out of Sight., no date. (Box 116, Folder 1)
      Based on the novel by Elmore Leonard. Universal Pictures.
    - Niccol, Andrew. The Truman Show., 1998. (Box 116, Folder 2)
      Paramount Pictures.
    - Irving, John. The Cider House Rules., no date. (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Payne, Alexander and Jim Taylor. Election., no date. (Box 116, Folder 4)
      Based on the novel by Tom Perrotta. MTV and Paramount pictures.
    - Elliott, Ted, et. al. Shrek., no date. (Box 116, Folder 5)
      Based on the book by William Steig. DreamWorks Pictures.
    - Fellowes, Julian. Gosford Park., 2001. (Box 116, Folder 6)
      Based upon an idea by Robert Altman and Bob Balaban.
    - Walsh, Fran, et. al. The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring., 2001. (Box 116, Folder 7)
      Based on the book by J.R.R. Tolkien. New Line Cinema.
    - Addica, Milo and Will Rokos. Monster's Ball., no date. (Box 116, Folder 8)
      Lion's Gate Films.
    - Affleck, Ben and Matt Damon. Good Will Hunting., no date. (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Shyamalan, M. Night. The Sixth Sense., no date. (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Minghella, Anthony. The Talented Mr. Ripley., 1999. (Box 117, Folder 2)
      Based on the novel by Patricia Highsmith. Paramount Pictures and Miramax Film Corp.
    - Crowe, Cameron. Almost Famous., 2000. (Box 117, Folder 3)
      Columbia Pictures and DreamWorks.
    - Cerami, Vincenzo and Roberto Benigni. Life is Beautiful., no date. (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Smith, Scott B. A Simple Plan., 1999. (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Franzoni, David, et. al. Gladiator., 2000. (Box 117, Folder 6)
      Universal and DreamWorks pictures.
    - Gaghan, Stephen. Traffic., no date. (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Kanin, Michael. Horse Opera., no date. (Box 117, Folder 8)
      Based on the original version of The Beggar's Opera.
    - Garfield, Brian. The Guns that Made the West Wild: A True Account., no date. (Box 117, Folder 9)
      Synopsis. Stanley Chase, producer.
    - Bridges, James. The Moving Finger., no date. (Box 117, Folder 10)
      Treatment for a movie musical. Stanley Chase, producer.
    - Foster, Alan Dean. You Won't Die, My Love., no date. (Box 118, Folder 1)
      Based on a short story by Robert Bloch. Stanley Chase Productions.
    - Chase, David. Love Her to Death., no date. (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Ferber, Edna., 1969. (Box 118, Folder 3)
      Assorted treatments and summaries.
    - Irish, William. Marihuana., no date. (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Kleiner, Harry and Stanley Chase. The Last Resort., no date. (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Kaufman, Bob. The Girl with ESP., no date. (Box 118, Folder 6)
      Created by Stanley Chase and Bob Kaufman.
    - Winder, Michael and Jan Hartman. Blood City., no date. (Box 118, Folder 7)
      Rearguard Productions, INC.
    - Hanalis, Blanche. Old Fish Hawk (folder 1 of 2)., 1978. (Box 118, Folder 8)
      Screenplay, Old Fish Hawk Company.
    - Hanalis, Blanche. Old Fish Hawk (folder 2 of 2)., 1978. (Box 118, Folder 9)
      Screenplay and Chase's executive producer binder.
    - Matheson, Richard. The Smell of Fear., no date. (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - O'Hanlon, George and Vernon Scott. Operation Piggie., 1967 July 13. (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Ludwig, Jerry. Fade In., 1968 April 3. (Box 119, Folder 3)
      Includes letter from Steve Kibler at the William Morris Agency.
    - Boileau-Narcejac. La Porte du Large., no date. (Box 119, Folder 4)
      Jerome Siegel Associates.
    - Sheers, J.C. Fire in His Hand., 1968. (Box 119, Folder 5)
      Universal City Studios.
    - Rudelson, Robert. Fools., no date. (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Kaufman, Philip. Freak., no date. (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Agee, James and Halsted Welles. The Blue Hotel., 1968 February 16. (Box 120, Folder 1)
      Second revised screenplay.
    - Ellis, David. Trial by Terror., 1966. (Box 120, Folder 2)
      Assorted screenplays with annotations.
    - Henerson, James. The Bystander., no date. (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Kingsley-Smith, Terence. Cactus., no date. (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Manaster, Benjamin. Carruthers., 1968. (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Change of Habit., 1968 June 12. (Box 120, Folder 6)
      First draft screenplay. Universal City Studios.
    - Stevens, Leslie. The Golden Flash., 1968 March 21. (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Crean, Robert. The Great American Hang-Up., 1968 March. (Box 121, Folder 2)
      Ashley Famous Agency.
    - Gardner, Gerald and Dee Caruso. How to Break up a Happy Marriage., no date. (Box 121, Folder 3)
      Based on the short story "Mortmain" by Graham Greene. CBS Films.
    - Livingston, Harold. Run for Your Life (Rendevous in Tokyo)., 1966 October 17. (Box 121, Folder 4)
      Roncom Films and Universal City Studios.
    - Rose, Reginald. The Hunt., no date. (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Fenton, Frank and Resner, Lawrence. How Many Graves to Los Perdidos?, no date. (Box 121, Folder 6)
      Synopsis
    - Manaster, Benjamin. Dixon., no date. (Box 121, Folder 7)
      Film treatment.
    - Peatman, Jim. He Who Rides the Whirlwind., no date. (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Husky, Rick. The Devil's Stronghold., no date. (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Dolan, Harry. No Strings., 1968 January 10. (Box 122, Folder 1)
      Step outline.
    - Heller, Joseph and George Mandel. Is Washington Square?, no date. (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Towne, Robert. The Long Ride Home., 1965 June 4. (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Smith, Charles B. A Killing on Thursday., no date. (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Dratler, Jay. The Judas Kiss., no date. (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Peters, Don. Ma., no date. (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Ulius, Betty. The Journey Back., no date. (Box 122, Folder 7)
      Story by Victor Stoloff and Betty Ulius.
    - Borisoff, Norman. Jetsam., 1968. (Box 122, Folder 8)
      Motion picture story.
    - Kaye, John. Marcus Stone Begins., 1968. (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Goodman, Don. Never Take a Mistress., no date. (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Joyce, Adrien. Interval., 1968. (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Becker, Robert. Incident at Up the Creek., no date. (Box 123, Folder 4)
      Western satire.
    - Turner, Frederic. Win Me Soon To Hell., no date. (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Giler, David. Together., no date. (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Yafa, Stephen. Paxton Quigley's Had the Course., 1968. (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Rosen, Milt. Shaman., no date. (Box 124, Folder 1)
      Outline.
    - Collins, Robert. Say, What Ever Happened to Harry Harrington?, no date. (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Cole, Tom and Joyce Chopra. Sposini., 1968. (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Ravetch, Irving and Harriet Frank, Jr. The Piano Sport., 1967. (Box 124, Folder 4)
      Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer INC. Produced by Katzka-Berne and Harold Loeb.
    - Greenberg, Stanley R. The Pedestal., 1967. (Box 124, Folder 5)
      Based on the novel by George Lanning. Red Mark Productions, INC.
    - Goff, Ivan and Ben Roberts. The Other Man., 1967 August 8. (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Felton, Earl. The Odyssey of Justice Lee., 1967 April 4. (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Mankiewicz, Tom. The Sweet Ride., 1967 July 19. (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Bridges, James. The Story of Frankenstein., no date. (Box 125, Folder 1)
      Screen treatment based on the work of Mary Shelley.
    - Driskill, William. The Suspect in the Twelfth House., no date. (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Sherman, Robert. Amigo., no date. (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Hammett, Dashiell. This King Business., no date. (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Alpert, Hollis. Doctor Monaco., no date. (Box 125, Folder 5)
      Screen treatment based on a short story by Thomas C. Turner.
    - Friedman, Bruce Jay. The Operator., 1965. (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Farrell, Henry. The Box Step., 1967 December 1. (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Matheson, Richard and William Nolan. Double, Double., no date. (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Karmel, Alex W. and Marjorie Low. Oblomov., 1956. (Box 125, Folder 9)
      Based on the novel by I.A. Goncharov.
    - Mittleman, Rick. Tower of Fear., no date. (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Antonioni, Michelangelo. Zabriskie Point., 1968. (Box 126, Folder 2)
      Carlo Ponti, producer. Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer INC.
    - Maddow, Ben. The Wind Machine., no date. (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Matheson, Richard. Progeny of the Adder., no date. (Box 126, Folder 4)
      Story outline based on the novel by Leslie H. Whitten.
    - Bridges, James. Choice Cuts., 1965 November 22. (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Goodman, David Zelag. The Crack Up., no date. (Box 126, Folder 6)
      Original story by Stanley Chase and David Zelag Goodman.
    - Poe, James. The Sergeant., no date. (Box 126, Folder 7)
      Based on the novel by Dennis Murphy.
    - Evans, Max. Shadow of Thunder., 1967 November 16. (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Maddow, Ben. The Counterfeit Man., no date. (Box 126, Folder 9)
- Series 3: Television, 1925-1994.; 32 boxes, 1 oversize box, 1 map folder.
  This series consists of production files and business files, publicity materials, ephemera, and scripts. Arranged in subseries A-D as follows:
  An American Christmas Carol, 1979-1994.
  The Courage of Kavik, the Wolf Dog, 1977-1983.
  Miscellaneous productions, 1925-1994.
  Scripts, 1960-1984.
  - Subseries 3A: An American Christmas Carol, 1979-1994.; 2 boxes.
    This subseries consists of business files and production files, photographs, publicity materials, and scripts. Co-produced by Stanley Chase Productions, An American Christmas Carol was a movie of the week for ABC. The screenplay was adapted from Charles Dickens' A Christmas Carol. It aired on December 16, 1979, was directed by Eric Till, and starred Henry Winkler.
    - Financial records and agreements., 1980-1994. (Box 127, Folder 1-6)
      Includes legal documents.
    - Financial records and agreements., 1987-1992. (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Photographic materials., 1979. (Box 128, Folder 2)
      Negatives, slides, portraits of the cast, and production stills.
    - Scripts., 1979. (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Music cue sheets., 1979. (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Press materials., 1979-1980. (Box 128, Folder 5)
      Reviews, publicity packets, and market ratings
    - Miscellaneous., 1979-1985. (Box 128, Folder 6)
      Assorted notes, letters, reviews, financial documents and records.
  - Subseries 3B:The Courage of Kavik, the Wolf Dog, 1977-1983.; 1.5 boxes.
    This subseries consists of business files and production files, photographs, publicity materials, and scripts. Produced by Stanley Chase Productions, The Courage of Kavik, the Wolf Dog was a two-hour television movie pilot for NBC. The screenplay was adapted from Walt Morey's novel, Kävik the Wolf Dog. It aired in the United States on January 20, 1980, and was directed by Peter Carter.
    - Shooting schedules, notes, and correspondence., 1977-1978. (Box 129, Folder 1)
      Shooting schedules, notes, and correspondence.
    - Budgets, correspondence, and agreements., 1977-1978. (Box 129, Folder 2)
      Budgets, correspondence, and agreements.
    - Contracts, agreements, correspondence., 1977-1979. (Box 129, Folder 3-5)
    - Press materials., 1979. (Box 129, Folder 6)
      Press kits and photographs.
    - Photographic materials., 1978-1979. (Box 130, Folder 1)
      Production stills and casting head shots.
    - Script., 1978 February 27. (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Agreements., 1983. (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 3C: Miscellaneous productions, 1925-1994.; 13.5 boxes, 1 oversize box, 1 map folder.
    This subseries consists of miscellaneous business files and production files, photographs, publicity materials, and scripts. Made for television movies include: Fear on Trial (Stanley Chase Productions and Alan Landsburg Productions, 1975); The Guardian (Stanley Chase Productions and HBO, 1984); and Grace Kelly (Stanley Chase Productions for Embassy / Kota, 1983). Universal Studios pilots include: Inside Danny Baker (created and developed for ABC with Mel Brooks, 1962); and Jigsaw (created and produced as a two-hour movie pilot for NBC, 1964). This subseries also includes assorted files from Chase's work at Metro-Goldwyn Mayer (MGM), Metromedia Producers Corporation, ABC, United Artists, and Columbia Pictures. The original contents of each file were maintained during processing.
    - The Guardian--Contracts, agreements, financial documents., 1983-1987. (Box 130, Folder 4-6)
      Includes budgets.
    - The Guardian--Miscellaneous., 1983-1984. (Box 131, Folder 1)
      Photographs, call sheets, scripts, and production reports.
    - The Guardian--Script., 1983. (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Fear on Trial--Miscellaneous., 1975. (Box 131, Folder 3)
      Correspondence, budgets, photographs, casting, and credits.
    - Fear on Trial--Contracts and agreements., 1975. (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Fear on Trial--Photographs., 1975. (Box 131, Folder 5-6)
      Prints of Chase on set. Contact sheets of production stills and 1/4" x 5" reel-to-reel video tape of location scouting.
    - Fear on Trial--Script. (Box 131, Folder 7)
      Final draft. Rintels, David.
    - Grace Kelly--Call sheets and schedules., 1982. (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Grace Kelly--Production binder (folder 1 of 3)., 1982. (Box 132, Folder 2)
      Casting, credits, call sheets, etc.
    - Grace Kelly--Production binder (folder 2 of 3)., 1982. (Box 132, Folder 3)
      Shooting schedules, location scouting, production costs and reports, and European shoot.
    - Grace Kelly--Production binder (folder 3 of 3)., 1982. (Box 132, Folder 4)
      Post-production looping and script.
    - Agreements, contracts, correspondence, and records for Stanley Chase Productions (folders 1-3 of 8)., 1981-1983. (Box 132, Folder 5-7)
      Includes documents relating to An American Christmas Carol, The Courage of Kavik, the Wolf Dog and Fish Hawk, and others.
    - Agreements, contracts, correspondence, and records for Stanley Chase Productions (folders 4- 8 of 8)., 1981-1983. (Box 133, Folder 1-5)
    - October Outcasts., 1971-1975. (Box 134, Folder 1)
      Miscellaneous documents.
    - Miscellaneous Stanley Chase productions., 1973-1976. (Box 134, Folder 2-3)
      Includes documents relating to Flint's Island and Red River.
    - Dorston Music., 1975-1983. (Box 134, Folder 4)
      Contracts and papers related to Stanley Chase's establishment of Dorston Music and a motion-picture production company. Includes production materials.
    - Wounded Knee research., no date. (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Synopsis and correspondence., 1971-1976. (Box 135, Folder 1)
      Pertaining to Back to the Wall and MGM pitches, and Alan Landsburg Productions.
    - MGM pitches and reader's reports., 1925-1975. (Box 135, Folder 2)
      Jack London stories.
    - Miscellaneous Stanley Chase productions synopsis and treatments (folder 1 of 3)., 1940-1975. (Box 135, Folder 3)
      Includes documents related to U.S.M.S.
    - Miscellaneous Stanley Chase productions synopsis and treatments (folder 2 of 3)., 1952-1972. (Box 135, Folder 4)
      Assorted scripts, memoranda, and synopsis.
    - Miscellaneous Stanley Chase productions synopsis and treatments (folder 3 of 3)., 1947-1975. (Box 135, Folder 5)
      Includes correspondence and research materials for various productions.
    - Jigsaw photographs., 1960-1970. (Box 136, Folder 1)
      Two-hour movie pilot produced and created by Chase for NBC, starring Jack Lord.
    - Jigsaw--Contracts, legal documents, and correspondence., 1964-1965. (Box 136, Folder 2-3)
    - Jigsaw--Miscellaneous., 1964-1966. (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Bubbly--Synopsis and production credits., 1973. (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Sweet Dreams--Contracts, legal documents, and correspondence., 1970. (Box 136, Folder 6-8)
    - Dream Wife--Contracts, legal documents, and correspondence., 1964-1973. (Box 137, Folder 1-2)
    - Dream Wife and Inside Danny Baker., 1973-1975. (Box 137, Folder 3)
      Assorted printed materials.
    - Inside Danny Baker and Dreams of Glory., 1962-1973. (Box 137, Folder 4-5)
    - Inside Danny Baker., 1962. (Box 137, Folder 6)
      Correspondence, synopsis, photos, casting, and credits.
    - Robert Kaufman and Stanley Chase vs. Screen Gems., 1973-1975. (Box 137, Folder 7)
      Legal documents.
    - Inside Danny Baker and A Time to Love., 1963. (Box 63)
      Preliminary production design drawings for Inside Danny Baker and two poster proofs for A Time to Love.
    - Lifeline pilots., 1965-1974. (Box 138, Folder 1)
      Assorted print materials, including budgets.
    - Blood on the Sun., 1972. (Box 138, Folder 2)
      Assorted print materials.
    - Landsburg Productions., 1973-1974. (Box 138, Folder 3-4)
    - Press materials., 1980-1994. (Box 138, Folder 5)
      Includes video cassette covers for Kavik and Fish Hawk.
    - Instant Justice., 1989-1992. (Box 138, Folder 6)
      Contracts and correspondence.
    - B.O.S.S. Headquarters--Production research., 1956-1964.; [2 folders]. (Box 139, Folder 1-2)
    - B.O.S.S. Headquarters--Script., 1964-1965. (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Screen Gems files., 1962-1964. (Box 139, Folder 4)
      Notes from a board room meeting (January, 1964) and various pilot ideas.
    - TV development journals (folder 1 of 2)., 1961-1962. (Box 139, Folder 5)
      Includes: Program Plans of the Independents, ABC Development 1961-1962, and Business Affairs.
    - TV development journals (folder 2 of 2)., 1961-1962. (Box 139, Folder 6)
      Includes: Program Plans of the Independents, and other development folder.